var myQuestions = [
	{
		question: "What is operating system?",
		answers: {
			a: 'collection of programs that manages hardware resources',
			b: 'system service provider to the application programs',
			c: 'link to interface the hardware and application programs',
                        d: 'all of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
	{
		question: "What is the main function of the command interpreter?",
		answers: {
			a: 'to get and execute the next user-specified command',
			b: 'to handle the files in operating system',
			c: 'to provide the interface between the API and application program',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "If a process fails, most operating system write the error information to a ______",
		answers: {
			a: 'log file',
			b: 'another running process',
			c: 'new file',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "To access the services of operating system, the interface is provided by the ___________ ",
		answers: {
			a: 'System calls',
			b: 'API',
			c: 'Library',
                        d: 'Assembly instructions'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "Which one of the following error will be handle by the operating system?",
		answers: {
			a: 'lack of paper in printer',
			b: 'connection failure in the network',
			c: 'power failure',
                        d: 'all of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
{
		question: "What is the ready state of a process?",
		answers: {
			a: 'when process is scheduled to run after some execution',
			b: 'when process is using the CPU',
			c: 'when process is unable to run until some task has been completed',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: " What is interprocess communication?",
		answers: {
			a: 'communication within the process',
			b: 'communication between two process',
			c: 'communication between two threads of same process',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "Which system call returns the process identifier of a terminated child?",
		answers: {
			a: 'wait',
			b: 'exit',
			c: 'fork',
                        d: 'get'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "In Unix, Which system call creates the new process??",
		answers: {
			a: 'fork',
			b: 'create',
			c: 'new',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "The systems which allow only one process execution at a time, are called __________",
		answers: {
			a: 'uniprogramming systems',
			b: 'uniprocessing systems',
			c: 'unitasking systems',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	}
];